btcsmash.io 2019-06-22

# BTC Smash!

### Privacy Policy

  1. **Introduction**

This Privacy Policy determines how your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is being used online. PII is described by the US privacy law and information security as information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. The following Privacy Policy informs how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our Website.

  2. **Personal Information Collection**

When visiting or registering on our website, as appropriate, you are only asked to enter your Bitcoin wallet address. We do not require for any emails, passwords, balance information or other sensitive personal information to be entered on this website.

  3. **Personal Information Usage**

We use the information we collect from you in order to enable the features of the website and personalize your experience. None of your entered data is visible to other users. 

  4. **Personal Information Protection**

We store as little data as possible to ensure delivery of all our Website features. We do not collect any sensitive personal data which could be used for making unauthorized payments or logins or to identify a person. We employ strict stored data protection measures.

  5. **Cookies**

We use small text files (Cookies) that the Website or its service provider or a third party transfers to your browser's memory. Cookies allow the Website to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to identify if you are logged in. We also use third party (Google Analytics) cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent in your browser settings. Turning off cookies completely will make some of the Website features (including signing up and logging in to restricted areas) not working.

  6. **Third-party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  7. **Third-party Links**

At our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. All information entered by you on any of the third-party websites is subject to their own privacy policy and this Website cannot be held liable for the usage of such information.

  8. **Google Products**

We use Google Analytics website traffic tracking system on our website. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses Cookies to track activity on our site. More information about opting-out of the use of the Google Cookies is provided in Google privacy policy.

  9. **California Online Privacy Protection Act Agreement**

According to California Online Privacy Protection Act, we agree that users can visit our site anonymously. We include the a link to the Privacy Policy as well as Terms of Service on all of our website subpages. Our Privacy Policy can easily be found on the Website and provides clear information on how we collect and manage personal information.

  10. **Children Online Privacy Protection Act**

We do not specifically market or provide services designed for children under the age of 13 years old.

  11. **CAN-SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**  
Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

  * To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

  12. **Privacy Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice by updating this page.

Return Home
